<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Look Above.</title>
    <description>This is where i post what i write from Novels, Peotry, Lyrics, Journals and More. Anything That Has A Purpose Or Interest Me. Here you can find my &lt;a href='https://music.younes.cf'&gt;Music&lt;/a&gt;, my &lt;a href='https://watch.younes.cf'&gt;Fav Series&lt;/a&gt;, and my &lt;a href='https://podcast.younes.cf'&gt;Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>http://younes.cf/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://younes.cf/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 14:07:12 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 14:07:12 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Happiness</title>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;
In the dark, a chase.
Something's be trying to hold me down
And leave me no hope on the ground.
I'm questioning my existential,
Desperately craving endlessly
Then you came to me genuinely
You loved me and i froze in time
How could I get lucky like this
               What have I done?

Where have i been all this time,
I'll never understand what's been going on my mind.
whenever i go i see you all around me.
Your shyness rings inside me.

Someone like me with someone like you
How unlikely too good to be true
When i see you and you see me.
How pleasant this feeling.
The moment you hold me, It woke me.
As we're walking in motion, time fades unknowingly
Myself sparks slowly as your voice consoles me.
We are laughing we are closer, its calming.
We are alone, we are hugging, its love.
I'm so glad know, how it feels to rest
on your soft shoulders,as i close my eyes
I hear your heartbeat, In your passion.
I was lost in an eternal bliss.

When i looked at my watch,
   Seeing its already time to leave.
I start looking in the bubble, the hours we spent.
I wonder if i could make minutes last forever,
I'd save up time and spend them with you.
I know its hard to believe, i know it isn't fair.
Knowing you'll always come back to me. lets me go.
As i'm walking away, I turn around watching u go
My eyes begin to tear, from being fulfilled with joy.

My love,
   Haven't you been told
Where ever i am
Where ever you'll be, i'll always go find you
I'd risk it all, For you anytime.
Words won't get enough of you
You're truly bittersweet taste of love
I' miss you everyday, every night, I'm sorry.
I'm grateful to have you by my side in all times
   As my friend, my partner, and my love.
              &lt;b&gt;I Love You F.B&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;em&gt;Save/Download&lt;/em&gt; This Piece From &lt;a href=&quot;https://younes.cf/pub/my-happiness.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 21:04:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/11/04/MyHappiness/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/11/04/MyHappiness/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Lyrics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Wanna</title>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;
It's the beat of my heart, the way i see it flowing
I didn't know, how it made me feel again,
You know i always thought it never returns
Oh will you let it show all it got again
Oh will you let it cross the line again
Oh Come towards me in the sky's above 
Where we can stay up all night 
              &lt;b&gt;For you&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;em&gt;Save/Download&lt;/em&gt; This Lyric From &lt;a href=&quot;https://younes.cf/pub/i-wanna.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/09/11/Mindless-Impression/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/09/11/Mindless-Impression/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Lyrics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Acceptance</title>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;
Jezz my bad, all this time you've proved me wrong
                                    how so?
Welcome to the other side of road, Look up in the mirror 
          watch the sadness and pain
Nothing matters than messing up more than once
Cause' feels like throwing up all together again
Forgot we ain't patient enough (Oh I need time)
Shit still hunts me its hard to fake how i feel
Every night i go out to get high, just for my memories to 
            make it worse
My body fighting to survive but my mind
            just wanna fucking die (wanna die)
I know how its hard to fake how you feel (I can see through)
Everywhere i go i see a blurry face in my memory (wasted)
My words might do nothing, but thats how i smoke my feelings
Its like smoking a blunt but letting it go away everytime
Inside my mind, still tryna make things work. Guess 
                    we all mentally ill (no shame about it)
I can hear the silence on the other side, just the side
Cause' It's not the end of the road
            Oh Feel it, ooh feel it, feel it (again)
These memories, they won't get the best of me .
            &lt;b&gt;So light up a joint for me&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;em&gt;View/Download&lt;/em&gt; This Lyrics From &lt;a href=&quot;https://younes.cf/pub/acceptance.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/04/27/Acceptance/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/04/27/Acceptance/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blank</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unflattered</title>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;
Look at me and watch, whats been redoubt
Takes my strength and my emotions away and see
I'm still delighting far away, ain't falling caus' ya
I forgot the convo days and phony nights
Splash of time blaze to doom
I've lost grip and turned into skyline
Make directions make it easy, unforgiving
Never mind, we're already doomed too soon
I've lost touch, i've said too much, been opposites and such. 
                                But i'lllll (what?)

Forget about dwelling what &quot;could've&quot; been
I saw you wasting time, tik-tok out of your mind
I don't blame ya for being unconscious all the time
I've seen enough, i've had too much, been unflattered and such. 
                                But I wish it waas alll ...
From my mind, from my mind, from my mind
From my mind, from my mind, from my mind
From my mind, from my mind, from my mind.
            &lt;!-- &lt;b&gt;For you&lt;/b&gt; --&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;em&gt;Save/Download&lt;/em&gt; This Lyrics From &lt;a href=&quot;https://younes.cf/pub/unflattered.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/04/26/Unflattered/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/04/26/Unflattered/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blank</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Slow Me</title>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;
I can't stand going fast at the times
My heartbeat rings like bell, silent and dim
I always thought i could make it on my own
        For forgetting embracin' thru
Wandering the lands looking for words to unmake it right
Chances flying, keep smackin' them all the time
Tell me something i don't know. Why can't u say
I know that's why you mind can't say, Ya know
    Lo'e, is like a sinking stone
        Drop it twice and it's begone
The story is different, i can feel it knocking
The story is different, bounce of lightening striking
The earth is spinning, with us time is moving
Slow me, Slow me, Slow me, Slow me
I'm moving way too fast, i'm getting away
Stop me thru, Slow me down, Losing myself
Its starting again, freshness of life glancing away
In-guided by new light crossing close to me 
Everyday,
You Turning away from me, from my mind
You Turning away from me, from my mind
Sometimes you can't be new but it's worth a try.
            &lt;!-- &lt;b&gt;For you&lt;/b&gt; --&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;em&gt;View/Download&lt;/em&gt; This Poem From &lt;a href=&quot;https://younes.cf/pub/slow_me.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/04/25/Slow-Me/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/04/25/Slow-Me/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blank</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Last Chapter</title>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;
Who thought it could've been like this for all i wished gone
Who thought it could've changed into a stranger's look away
I remember, I remember seeing you for the first time.
I remember walking up puzzeled trying match perfect things
I remember last time the happiness and pain.
I remember whats all left just memories (now memories)
So why can't i lose all the momories now, why can't i
So much sacrificed for left by unwakened dream
I'm trapped in this sordid game, where the ending's
                                          All the same


I tried to heal your heart with all that i could
                              But got mine broken instead
Ever since the day you left my fate been set alone
Tell me how many years to walk this path alone? (again)
So much we planned ahead, so why'd you choose to leave
                              Why cant i?
Nothing is harder than to wake up all alone, Realize
    it's not okay, it's the end of all we known
Time keeps passing by but its seems frozen still
Tell me do you still even feel a thing?
Scars are left behind but some too deep to feel
And i've lost my power to feel anymore
Gave you all i had to give, i hope its worth it

When all is gone and can't be regained
    We can't seem to shelter the pain inside
The pain is strong and urges rise, your pain is gone
Time shows now I think I understand my mistake
Like a memoir i saw it through, In the end
                        I'd give my life for you.
Once i stood so tall now i'm searching for a sign
Nothing lasts forever for all good times we had
    I'd choose to trade it all to bring you back
Some day, some-day when you'll open your mind
You'll find a mistake that dragged us all behind
Non' can't be real, u took a piece of me with you.
Cause' If you'd only see the picture's clear as today, 
                        you'd still be around

Oooh I can hear the voice's wanting you to stay, 
    I suppress them voice's cause' ain't gonna be the same 
They say all love can never die, I say it just moves on
Oh, i don't need your regret apologizes. Save it for another time
Cause we all just need a reason, a reason to stay
But some can't be bothered to stay for another day
Oh I ain't worried about anything no more
Cause' there's somebody that will love us all
But if we can't be in no relationship with this person and 
    make it work
How you gonn' go be in another relationship and 
    make it work, it's the same thing


It's the end of the road, the last chapter remains
Found a place for you in my mind, where you can stay away
Everything can finally fade, I hope you find your own way
What's left to find, the big prize wasted and the days are gone.

                                           &lt;b&gt;Thank you, Good-bye&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;em&gt;View/Download&lt;/em&gt; This Lyrics From &lt;a href=&quot;https://younes.cf/pub/last_chapter.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/04/01/Last-Chapter/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/04/01/Last-Chapter/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Blank</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ana Jay</title>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;
Wa chof fin wslat
B9it kantsana o kantsana
chkon kan kaygol, tri9 fin ghadi twaslna
Klit d9a f9albi, ob9it sakt
dawiti 3liya dnya okhalitini kanbghik
9lila fha9ek had stora
Masm3tch lharda
kola chhal hadi nsit o khwit
No,no Bzaff tlhob lik
Hbiba, 9albk dima kaysoni
Jamais n3awdo nafs lghalat
We chof dnya chhal sghira
9albi chwiya o tfara
lbarh bohdi O lyoum hdaya
F 3ini kanchofk wf 9albi 9albk
love 3amri antal9k mazal
No, no bzaff
    Mab9a walo
            &lt;b&gt;For you&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;em&gt;Save/Download&lt;/em&gt; This Poem From &lt;a href=&quot;https://younes.cf/pub/ana_jay.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/03/13/Ana-Jay/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/03/13/Ana-Jay/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Poem</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Wanna</title>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;
When i hear your voice
I'd look at the roof
   And think of everyway
   I'd see you soon
If you'd look at the sky
   You'd know..
   I ain't far away
I wanna get you more, often
   To see your joy
   To take you on up
   To hold you under
   To kiss you undone
I'd never seek a better
       Being your lover
I've got a feeling for you
       Nothing else matter
              &lt;b&gt;For you&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;em&gt;Save/Download&lt;/em&gt; This Poem From &lt;a href=&quot;https://younes.cf/pub/i_wanna.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/03/05/I-Wanna/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/03/05/I-Wanna/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Poem</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Give Me A Sign</title>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;
I can't hold myself anymore.
Hopelessly waiting for you to come.
Thinking of the times that we have.
I keep my mind for you, to stay.
Holding back, hoping for you to ask.

I have see myself turning into dark
    Losing my existence everyday.
    Don't wanna see myself replacing you.
I know that you are afraid.
    So just let me show you.
    There is no one in the world than you
    Who has won my heart.
I will forgiving you for hurting myself. As
    Sometimes thru all of the things
    We think and say love can be a breath away

I lost you once but don't want to lose you twice.
        Will you ever make a sign
                    &lt;b&gt;For you&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;em&gt;Save/Download&lt;/em&gt; This Poem From &lt;a href=&quot;https://younes.cf/pub/come_back.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/02/24/ComeBack/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/02/24/ComeBack/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Poem</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bleak Of Reality</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 22:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://younes.cf/posts/2022/02/22/Bleak-Of-Reality/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://younes.cf/posts/2022/02/22/Bleak-Of-Reality/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Novel</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
